{
  "title": "Pop Music",
  "topic": "66fec2c9b6950e88826fe005",
  "difficulty": "easy",
  "num_questions": 12,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is known as the 'Queen of Pop'?",
      "options": [
        "Madonna",
        "Beyoncé",
        "Taylor Swift",
        "Lady Gaga"
      ],
      "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the famous pop group that includes members such as Justin Timberlake and Britney Spears?",
      "options": [
        "Backstreet Boys",
        "NSYNC",
        "One Direction",
        "The Jackson 5"
      ],
      "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which pop star is known for the hit song 'Bad Romance'?",
      "options": [
        "Katy Perry",
        "Rihanna",
        "Lady Gaga",
        "Ariana Grande"
      ],
      "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the title of Taylor Swift's debut album?",
      "options": [
        "Fearless",
        "1989",
        "Taylor Swift",
        "Red"
      ],
      "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which song by Katy Perry features the lyrics 'Do you ever feel like a plastic bag'?",
      "options": [
        "Firework",
        "Roar",
        "Teenage Dream",
        "Last Friday Night"
      ],
      "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the stage name of the artist born Stefani Joanne Angelina Germanotta?",
      "options": [
        "Beyoncé",
        "Kesha",
        "Lady Gaga",
        "Ariana Grande"
      ],
      "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which artist released the album '25' in 2015?",
      "options": [
        "Adele",
        "Ed Sheeran",
        "Bruno Mars",
        "Demi Lovato"
      ],
      "correct_option": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is known for the song 'Shape of You'?",
      "options": [
        "Justin Bieber",
        "Ed Sheeran",
        "Shawn Mendes",
        "Maroon 5"
      ],
      "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What genre of music is typically associated with artists like Billie Eilish and Halsey?",
      "options": [
        "Rock",
        "Pop",
        "Jazz",
        "Country"
      ],
      "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which pop singer's real name is Robyn Fenty?",
      "options": [
        "Ariana Grande",
        "Rihanna",
        "Nicki Minaj",
        "Demi Lovato"
      ],
      "correct_option": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the popular music festival held annually in Coachella Valley, California?",
      "options": [
        "Lollapalooza",
        "Bonnaroo",
        "Coachella",
        "Glastonbury"
      ],
      "correct_option": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which pop artist is known for the song 'Blinding Lights'?",
      "options": [
        "The Weeknd",
        "Drake",
        "Post Malone",
        "Maroon 5"
      ],
      "correct_option": 1
    }
  ]
}